https://www.lakeballs.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This is the internet privacy policy for www.lakeballs.com (the “Website”)
This website is the property of Lakeballs. We take the privacy of all visitors to this Website very seriously and therefore set out in this privacy and cookies policy our position regarding certain privacy matters and the use of cookies on this Website.
This policy covers all data that is shared by a visitor with us whether directly via www.lakeballs.com or via email. This policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you share with us, or that we collect from you either directly via this Website or via email.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 we can be contacted via email at info@lakeballs.com.
1.         Information we collect
In operating our Website we may collect and process the following data about you:
1.1       Details of your visits to our Website and the resources that you access including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblog statistics and other communication data.
1.2       Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website, such as when you register to receive information such as a newsletter, place an order or contact us via the contact us page.
1.3       Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.
2.         Use of cookies
On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services, and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our Website.
Such information will not identify you personally, it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. It is used by us to analyse how visitors interact with the Website so that we can continue to develop and improve this Website.
We may gather information about your general Internet use by using a cookie file that is downloaded to your computer. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically.  This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our Website and the service that we provide to you.
All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular areas of our Website.
Any advertising featured on this Website may also incorporate cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our Website.
3.         Use of your information
The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:
3.1       To provide you with information requested from us relating to our products or services and to provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you if you have consented to receive such information.
3.2       To meet our contractual commitments to you.
3.3       To notify you about any changes to our Website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.
3.4       If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.
3.5       We may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We or they may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented to at the time your information was collected.
3.6       If you are a new customer, we will only contact you or allow third parties to contact you only when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for.
3.7       If you do not want us to use your data for ourselves or third parties you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us on the form on which we collect your data.
3.8       Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors such as your area of residence or age group.
4.         Storing your personal data
4.1       We may transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Economic area for processing and storing. In addition, it may be processed by staff operating outside the European Economic area who work for us or for one of our suppliers. For example, such staff may be engaged in the processing and concluding of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this privacy policy.
4.2       Data that is provided to us is stored on secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into via our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.
4.3       The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and the  transmission of such data is entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain areas of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.
5.         Disclosing your information
5.1       Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our company.
5.2       We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:
5.2.1    Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.
5.2.2    Where we are legally required to disclose your information.
5.2.3    To assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.
6.         Third party links
You might find links to third party websites on our Website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.
7.         Access to information
The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Please note that any demand for access may be subject to payment of a small fee which covers our costs in providing you with the information requested. Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact us page on our website.
8.         Contacting us
We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this policy please do not hesitate to contact us at info@lakeballs.com.
If you would prefer to write to us then our contact address is LakeBalls.com, Unit 1, 11-13 Roebuck Road, Hainault, Essex, IG6 3TU.
DELIVERY PRICES
GRADING GUIDE
ABOUT US
Lake balls vary in quality. Please do not confuse our golf balls with some of the inferior products sold by some retailers. Take a look at our grading guide to help you choose the quality of golf ball you need and remember we will refund or replace if not completely satisfied.
Home
GRADING GUIDE
CONTACT US
ABOUT US
MY ACCOUNT
SITE MAP
Customer Service
Terms & Conditions
Subscribe
Lakeballs.com11-13 Roebuck Road, Hainault Business Park, Hainault, Essex IG6 3TU
About us
Customer Services
Contact us
Cookies
© 2020 Lakeballs. All Rights Reserved.
This website requires cookies to provide all of its features. For more information on what data is contained in the cookies, please see our Privacy Policy page. To accept cookies from this site, please click the Allow button.
Allow
